# **Nurul Uhkrowi**

# Full-Stack Web Developer

+628977031387 | uhkrowi@gmail.com

https://uhkrowi.github.io

#### **PROFILE**

I am a web developer with years of experience, I have passions for all things new and interesting in tech industry. With a 'jack-of-all-trades' mindset I have learned and worked as a mobile and desktop app developer, hardware integrator and automation app maker.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Dec 2021 - Present

### **Back-End Web Developer**

PT Astra International Tbk

As a body hire from PT BeIT, join into Astra team to modify their existing system and focusing on tax regulation.

Tech stacks: .NET, C#, SQL Server.

Jan 2020 - Present

### Front-End Web Developer

PT BelT Inovasi Tiwikrama

Creating prototypes based on mockups, integrating with web services of enterprise Data Center Management system, and do back-end stuffs when necessary.

Tech stacks: Javascript, Vue.js, Tailwind CSS.

Sep 2021 - Nov 2021

### Front-End Web Developer

PT Perjalanan Menembus Galaksi

Working on designing & creating web components of an online shop back office.

Tech stacks: Javascript, Vue.js, Nuxt.js.

Nov 2017 - Oct 2019

# Back-End Web Developer

PT Ink & Canvas

Building an enterprise system for one of learning institutions in Indonesia. Some of the services are Academic, E-Learning, Human Resource and Finance.

Tech stacks: .NET, C#, PostgreSQL, Microsoft Azure.

Feb 2016 - Nov 2017

### Full-Stack Web Developer

PT IndoVisual Presentatama

Developing smart home and office from scratch, integrating hardwares to control and automate them with system.

Tech stacks: PHP, Javascript, NodeJS, AngularJS, Java, Mobile, Raspberry Pi, MySQL, SQLite.

#### **SKILL**

- HTML
- CSS
- Go
- Javascript
- NodeJS
- React.is
- Vue.js
- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- Git
- Wordpress
- Microsoft Azure

#### **EDUCATION**

2013 - 2016

### Information Technology

LP3I Jakarta

#### **PROJECT**

Jan 2022 - Mar 2021

### Company Profile zumstar.com

Company Profile Website of Zumstar (product of Graha Multimedia Nusantara).

Jan 2022 - Mar 2021

### Company Profile gmn.com

Company Profile Website of Graha Multimedia Nusantara.

Oct 2021 - Dec 2021

# **Rental Housing**

Rental flat, private and public housing in Indonesia for low economic citizen, supply and demand management of properties, facilitate citizen to book and rent house with ease.

Aug 2019 - Oct 2019

### **Booking Room**

A mobile application for scheduling meeting with booking available rooms feature, note of MOM, participants invitation, extending meeting time if possible, order meals to the pantry, etc.

Mar 2020 - Apr 2020

### Ship Rental Management

Ship rent management aim to ease fishermen to rent ships, including picking type of ship, setting rental period, extending the period, monitoring their payment. the application also helps the owners of rental to manage information about ships, their customers, payments and reports.

Nov 2017 - Oct 2019

# **English Learning Institution ERP**

Resource planning, monitoring and management of many modules that help user to manage data of students, employees, learning processes, payments, etc. Features: Dashboards, Integration of many modules as microservices (academic, human resource, elearning, finance, general data, usermanagement).

Feb 2016 - Nov 2017

# **Smart Home & Office**

Mobile and Web app for managing, controlling and monitoring devices at home e.g lamp/light, door lock, TV, CCTV, air conditioner, curtain, switch, sensors, etc. It's main features are: Managing, Controlling and monitoring devices, Configuration, User management, Role, Permission, etc.